[{"body": [{"type": "number-of-figure", "title": "填一填", "stem": "哪组有", "num": 6, "unit": "个", "name": "方块", "list": [{"img": "v2/通用/基本平面图形/正方形_1.svg", "num": 6}, {"img": "v2/通用/基本平面图形/正方形_1.svg", "num": 7}]}], "answers": [0], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的认识"], "level": "1", "type": "选择", "number": "1-1-9-08"}, {"body": [{"type": "number-of-figure", "title": "填一填", "stem": "哪组有", "num": 6, "unit": "个", "name": "方块", "list": [{"img": "v2/通用/基本平面图形/正方形_1.svg", "num": 6}, {"img": "v2/通用/基本平面图形/正方形_1.svg", "num": 8}]}], "answers": [0], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的认识"], "level": "1", "type": "选择", "number": "1-1-9-08"}, {"body": [{"type": "number-of-figure", "title": "填一填", "stem": "哪组有", "num": 9, "unit": "个", "name": "方块", "list": [{"img": "v2/通用/基本平面图形/正方形_1.svg", "num": 6}, {"img": "v2/通用/基本平面图形/正方形_1.svg", "num": 9}]}], "answers": [1], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的认识"], "level": "1", "type": "选择", "number": "1-1-9-08"}, {"body": [{"type": "number-of-figure", "title": "填一填", "stem": "哪组有", "num": 10, "unit": "个", "name": "方块", "list": [{"img": "v2/通用/基本平面图形/正方形_1.svg", "num": 6}, {"img": "v2/通用/基本平面图形/正方形_1.svg", "num": 10}]}], "answers": [1], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的认识"], "level": "1", "type": "选择", "number": "1-1-9-08"}, {"body": [{"type": "number-of-figure", "title": "填一填", "stem": "哪组有", "num": 6, "unit": "个", "name": "方块", "list": [{"img": "v2/通用/基本平面图形/正方形_1.svg", "num": 7}, {"img": "v2/通用/基本平面图形/正方形_1.svg", "num": 6}]}], "answers": [1], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的认识"], "level": "1", "type": "选择", "number": "1-1-9-08"}, {"body": [{"type": "number-of-figure", "title": "填一填", "stem": "哪组有", "num": 7, "unit": "个", "name": "方块", "list": [{"img": "v2/通用/基本平面图形/正方形_1.svg", "num": 7}, {"img": "v2/通用/基本平面图形/正方形_1.svg", "num": 8}]}], "answers": [0], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的认识"], "level": "1", "type": "选择", "number": "1-1-9-08"}, {"body": [{"type": "number-of-figure", "title": "填一填", "stem": "哪组有", "num": 7, "unit": "个", "name": "方块", "list": [{"img": "v2/通用/基本平面图形/正方形_1.svg", "num": 7}, {"img": "v2/通用/基本平面图形/正方形_1.svg", "num": 9}]}], "answers": [0], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的认识"], "level": "1", "type": "选择", "number": "1-1-9-08"}, {"body": [{"type": "number-of-figure", "title": "填一填", "stem": "哪组有", "num": 10, "unit": "个", "name": "方块", "list": [{"img": "v2/通用/基本平面图形/正方形_1.svg", "num": 7}, {"img": "v2/通用/基本平面图形/正方形_1.svg", "num": 10}]}], "answers": [1], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的认识"], "level": "1", "type": "选择", "number": "1-1-9-08"}, {"body": [{"type": "number-of-figure", "title": "填一填", "stem": "哪组有", "num": 6, "unit": "个", "name": "方块", "list": [{"img": "v2/通用/基本平面图形/正方形_1.svg", "num": 8}, {"img": "v2/通用/基本平面图形/正方形_1.svg", "num": 6}]}], "answers": [1], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的认识"], "level": "1", "type": "选择", "number": "1-1-9-08"}, {"body": [{"type": "number-of-figure", "title": "填一填", "stem": "哪组有", "num": 8, "unit": "个", "name": "方块", "list": [{"img": "v2/通用/基本平面图形/正方形_1.svg", "num": 8}, {"img": "v2/通用/基本平面图形/正方形_1.svg", "num": 7}]}], "answers": [0], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的认识"], "level": "1", "type": "选择", "number": "1-1-9-08"}, {"body": [{"type": "number-of-figure", "title": "填一填", "stem": "哪组有", "num": 8, "unit": "个", "name": "方块", "list": [{"img": "v2/通用/基本平面图形/正方形_1.svg", "num": 8}, {"img": "v2/通用/基本平面图形/正方形_1.svg", "num": 9}]}], "answers": [0], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的认识"], "level": "1", "type": "选择", "number": "1-1-9-08"}, {"body": [{"type": "number-of-figure", "title": "填一填", "stem": "哪组有", "num": 10, "unit": "个", "name": "方块", "list": [{"img": "v2/通用/基本平面图形/正方形_1.svg", "num": 8}, {"img": "v2/通用/基本平面图形/正方形_1.svg", "num": 10}]}], "answers": [1], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的认识"], "level": "1", "type": "选择", "number": "1-1-9-08"}, {"body": [{"type": "number-of-figure", "title": "填一填", "stem": "哪组有", "num": 6, "unit": "个", "name": "方块", "list": [{"img": "v2/通用/基本平面图形/正方形_1.svg", "num": 9}, {"img": "v2/通用/基本平面图形/正方形_1.svg", "num": 6}]}], "answers": [1], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的认识"], "level": "1", "type": "选择", "number": "1-1-9-08"}, {"body": [{"type": "number-of-figure", "title": "填一填", "stem": "哪组有", "num": 9, "unit": "个", "name": "方块", "list": [{"img": "v2/通用/基本平面图形/正方形_1.svg", "num": 9}, {"img": "v2/通用/基本平面图形/正方形_1.svg", "num": 7}]}], "answers": [0], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的认识"], "level": "1", "type": "选择", "number": "1-1-9-08"}, {"body": [{"type": "number-of-figure", "title": "填一填", "stem": "哪组有", "num": 9, "unit": "个", "name": "方块", "list": [{"img": "v2/通用/基本平面图形/正方形_1.svg", "num": 9}, {"img": "v2/通用/基本平面图形/正方形_1.svg", "num": 8}]}], "answers": [0], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的认识"], "level": "1", "type": "选择", "number": "1-1-9-08"}, {"body": [{"type": "number-of-figure", "title": "填一填", "stem": "哪组有", "num": 9, "unit": "个", "name": "方块", "list": [{"img": "v2/通用/基本平面图形/正方形_1.svg", "num": 9}, {"img": "v2/通用/基本平面图形/正方形_1.svg", "num": 10}]}], "answers": [0], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的认识"], "level": "1", "type": "选择", "number": "1-1-9-08"}, {"body": [{"type": "number-of-figure", "title": "填一填", "stem": "哪组有", "num": 10, "unit": "个", "name": "方块", "list": [{"img": "v2/通用/基本平面图形/正方形_1.svg", "num": 10}, {"img": "v2/通用/基本平面图形/正方形_1.svg", "num": 6}]}], "answers": [0], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的认识"], "level": "1", "type": "选择", "number": "1-1-9-08"}, {"body": [{"type": "number-of-figure", "title": "填一填", "stem": "哪组有", "num": 10, "unit": "个", "name": "方块", "list": [{"img": "v2/通用/基本平面图形/正方形_1.svg", "num": 10}, {"img": "v2/通用/基本平面图形/正方形_1.svg", "num": 7}]}], "answers": [0], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的认识"], "level": "1", "type": "选择", "number": "1-1-9-08"}, {"body": [{"type": "number-of-figure", "title": "填一填", "stem": "哪组有", "num": 10, "unit": "个", "name": "方块", "list": [{"img": "v2/通用/基本平面图形/正方形_1.svg", "num": 10}, {"img": "v2/通用/基本平面图形/正方形_1.svg", "num": 8}]}], "answers": [0], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的认识"], "level": "1", "type": "选择", "number": "1-1-9-08"}, {"body": [{"type": "number-of-figure", "title": "填一填", "stem": "哪组有", "num": 9, "unit": "个", "name": "方块", "list": [{"img": "v2/通用/基本平面图形/正方形_1.svg", "num": 10}, {"img": "v2/通用/基本平面图形/正方形_1.svg", "num": 9}]}], "answers": [1], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的认识"], "level": "1", "type": "选择", "number": "1-1-9-08"}]